

phone: (778) 989-6449 | email: jagperlas@gmail.com

Profile

BCIT Computer Information Technology student who takes initiative and has high standards in his own work and in group work. I bring experience in leadership and enthusiastic communication to motivate my peers and create a strong chemistry to produce the best results.

Technical Skills

Programming	OS	IT	Software
Python	Windows 7, 8, 10	CCNA	Microsoft Office
C#	Windows Server 2019	CompTIA A+	MySQL
Bash	Linux, Kali Linux	HP & RICOH Printers	Adobe Creative Cloud
MEAN Stack	MacOS 13,14,15	Audio/Visual	Cisco Meraki
	iOS, TVOS	Computer Hardware	Sophos

Experience

Information Technology Intern

Dec 2020 - Dec 2021

York House School

- Provided IT support to over 700 students and 100 staff members via phone call and SolarWinds HelpDesk, troubleshooting, diagnosing, and contacting third-party vendors if needed to ensure problem resolution
- Managed and inventoried over 200 Apple devices including MacBooks, iMacs, iPads and Apple TVs using Mosyle MDM
- Provided and assisted with A/V related tech, including full theatre assemblies and recordings
- Established a Cache Server on a Mac Mini to increase software update download speeds by 100%
- Acted and played as the school mascot, Teggy the Tiger

Rides Operator

Jun 2017 - Sep 2018

Pacific National Exhibition (PNE)

- Demonstrated professionalism and communicated enthusiastically towards various kinds of customers
- Troubleshooted mechanical problems within the train regarding speed, daily maintenance, and loose parts

Academic Projects

Smart Roster Schedule | | Algorithms Team

Dec 2020

BCIT Industry Sponsored Student Projects || Team of 7

- Developed main algorithm to automate nurse-patient assignments efficiently to solve main problem statement about saving time and reducing human error
- Wrote a research paper about implementing a meta-heuristic approach by using SQL and Simulated Annealing
- Won 1st place in the BCIT ISSP Expo

Outbreak: Source | | Lead Developer

May 2020

BCIT Agile Methodology Course | | Team of 6

- Developed an API heavy idle-game application using the Agile development process and MEAN stack
- Completed 70% of code, specialized in backend, database, and core mechanics of the game
- Technologies used: MongoDB, Express.Js, Angular, Node.Js, GitHub
- https://github.com/jperlas2019/Outbreak-Source

Python MP3 Player | Lead Developer

Mar - Apr 2020

BCIT Object-Oriented Programming Course || Group of 3

- Programmed a music player using Python object-oriented fundamentals with a database and GUI
- Connected SQLite, VLC, and Tkinter to work together and play mp3 files from user's harddrive
- Technologies used: Python, SQLite, VLC, Tkinter, GitHub, Postman, eyeD3 module



jaguarperlas.com

linkedin.com/in/jaguar-perlas

phone: (778) 989-6449 || email: jagperlas@gmail.com

Personal Projects

Combo Swipe May 2020 - Present

Unity Mobile Game

- Currently developing a single player 2D RPG mobile game using Unity and C#
- Programmed multiple data structures for the core mechanics of the game
- Implemented formulas for health, player stats, attack damage, and probability
- Conducted constant manual testing to decrease the potential of bugs and exploits
- Technologies used: Unity, C#

Education

Computer Information Technology Diploma British Columbia Institute of Technology, GPA 86% Sept 2019 - Present

Certificates

Cisco Certified Network Associate CompTIA A+

In progress In progress